{"items": [{"question": "befitting a brother or brothers", "answer": "fraternal", "options": ["uxorious", "uxorial", "fraternal", "sorority"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A social club for female undergraduates", "answer": "sorority", "options": ["uxorial", "sorority", "henpecked", "uxorious"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "submissive to your wife", "answer": "uxorious", "options": ["uxorial", "marital", "henpecked", "uxorious"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Befitting a wife", "answer": "uxorial", "options": ["regal", "marital", "uxorial", "henpecked"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Harassed by persistent nagging", "answer": "henpecked", "options": ["regal", "marital", "incendiary", "henpecked"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "relating to the state of marriage", "answer": "marital", "options": ["arson", "marital", "regal", "incendiary"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Belonging to a supreme ruler", "answer": "regal", "options": ["arsonist", "incendiary", "arson", "regal"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Involving deliberate burning of property", "answer": "incendiary", "options": ["klpetomania", "arsonist", "arson", "incendiary"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Malicious burning to destroy property", "answer": "arson", "options": ["arson", "arsonist", "klpetomania", "dipsomania"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A criminal who illegally sets fire to property", "answer": "arsonist", "options": ["pyromania", "arsonist", "klpetomania", "dipsomania"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "An irresistible impulse to steal in the absence of any economic motive", "answer": "klpetomania", "options": ["dipsomania", "pyromania", "klpetomania", "megalomania"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "an uncontrollable craving for alcoholic liquors", "answer": "dipsomania", "options": ["dipsomania", "nymphomania", "pyromania", "megalomania"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "An uncontrollable desire to set fire to things", "answer": "pyromania", "options": ["nymphomania", "satyromania", "pyromania", "megalomania"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A mania of delusions of grandeur", "answer": "megalomania", "options": ["nymphomania", "claustrophobia", "satyromania", "megalomania"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Abnormally intense sexual desire in women", "answer": "nymphomania", "options": ["agoraphobia", "claustrophobia", "satyromania", "nymphomania"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Abnormally intense sexual desire in men", "answer": "satyromania", "options": ["claustrophobia", "satyromania", "agoraphobia", "acrophobia"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "A morbid fear of being closed in a confined space", "answer": "claustrophobia", "options": ["claustrophobia", "fraternal", "acrophobia", "agoraphobia"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A morbid fear of open spaces", "answer": "agoraphobia", "options": ["fraternal", "sorority", "agoraphobia", "acrophobia"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A morbid fear of great heights", "answer": "acrophobia", "options": ["fraternal", "uxorious", "acrophobia", "sorority"], "answer_index": 3}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 30.txt", "total": 19}